<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sc0rpi0n&#39;s Journey</title>
    <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sc0rpi0n&#39;s Journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: The Final Week</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-12-the-final-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-12-the-final-week/</guid>
      <description>“Software is like entropy: It is difficult to grasp, weighs nothing, and obeys the Second Law of Thermodynamics; i.e., it always increases.”  — Norman Augustine
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week will be the last week of coding for GSoC 2019. It is time to finish work now.
 The C Parser Travis Build Tests Documentation  The C Parser I completed the C Parser last week along with the documentation for the module.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11: The Other Parser</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-11-the-other-parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-11-the-other-parser/</guid>
      <description>Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about the C parser.
 The Fortran Parser The C Parser Documentation Travis Build  The Fortran Parser The Fortran Parser is complete. The Pull Request has also been merged. The parser is merged in master and will be a part of the next SymPy release. You can check out the source code for the Parser at the Pull Request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10: The Finished Parser</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-10-the-finished-parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/08/week-10-the-finished-parser/</guid>
      <description>“Software is like entropy: It is difficult to grasp, weighs nothing, and obeys the Second Law of Thermodynamics; i.e., it always increases.”  — Norman Augustine
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and we will talk all about the Fortran Parser this week. I have passed the second evaluation and Fortran Parser pull request is complete.
 The Week Fortran Parser SymPy Expression Travis Builds The C Parser The Meeting  The Week This week began with me working on the C parser to finalize that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9: It&#39;s the Evaluation Week!!</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-9-its-the-evaluation-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-9-its-the-evaluation-week/</guid>
      <description>Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this time we will be talking about the second evaluation for GSoC. The main objective of the week was to get the Fortran parser ready.
 The Fortran Parser Traivs and the Tests LFortran Evaluation!!! The meeting What Now  The Fortran Parser The Fortran parser is finally complete after shifting to using SymPy&amp;rsquo;s codegen AST. It can now parser all the stuff that the parser could do before shifting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8:Boys!! We got a Plan.</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-8boys-we-got-a-plan./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-8boys-we-got-a-plan./</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Those who plan do better than those who do not plan even though they rarely stick to their plan.&amp;rdquo; ― Winston Churchill
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week I have some good news for you all. We have got a few plans to get the progress of the project rolling as the second evaluation approaches. The meeting also took place this week, so, after waiting for so long, we have some good insights from the meeting this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7:A Little Step Towards Consistency</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-7a-little-step-towards-consistency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-7a-little-step-towards-consistency/</guid>
      <description>“It&amp;rsquo;s not what we do once in a while that shapes our lives. It&amp;rsquo;s what we do consistently.”  ― Anthony Robbins
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to be more consistent with my schedule, work and communications with the Organization. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken a few small steps and plan to improve as I keep working.
 Consistency!? Merging the Pull Requests?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6: The Most Chaotic Week Ever!!</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-6-the-most-chaotic-week-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/07/week-6-the-most-chaotic-week-ever/</guid>
      <description>“A language that doesn&amp;rsquo;t affect the way you think about programming is not worth knowing.”  ― Alan J. Perlis
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week was one of the most chaotic weeks till now if not the most chaotic. I had to move places as the Uni opens next week, had the summer classes exams and had to convert the C parser to use SymPy&amp;rsquo;s Codegen AST from Python AST all in one week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5: The Evaluation is here: End of Phase 1</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-5-the-evaluation-is-here-end-of-phase-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-5-the-evaluation-is-here-end-of-phase-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On two occasions I have been asked [by members of Parliament!]: &amp;lsquo;Pray, Mr. Babbage, if you put into the machine wrong figures, will the right answers come out ?&amp;rsquo; I am not able rightly to apprehend the kind of confusion of ideas that could provoke such a question.&amp;rdquo; — Charles Babbage
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week was the last week of Phase-1 and the evaluations for the first phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4: The Fortran Parser is finally here</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-4-the-fortran-parser-is-finally-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-4-the-fortran-parser-is-finally-here/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When someone says: &amp;lsquo;I want a programming language in which I need only say what I wish done&amp;rsquo;, give him a lollipop.&amp;rdquo;  — Alan J. Perlis in Software Metrics
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week has been relatively a little odd. The week started a little slow but slowly it turned out to be a good and productive week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3: What&#39;s Happening? Where have I been?</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-3-whats-happening-where-have-i-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-3-whats-happening-where-have-i-been/</guid>
      <description>“How did it get so late so soon?”  ― Dr. Seuss
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and we&amp;rsquo;re running late on everything this week. This time we will talk about some operating system stuff along with the week&amp;rsquo;s work. I will have more blogs on operating systems and that type of stuff soon. For now, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what&amp;rsquo;s happening.
Why so Late?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: A Tale of The Illusive Pull Request</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-2-a-tale-of-the-illusive-pull-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-2-a-tale-of-the-illusive-pull-request/</guid>
      <description>In real open source, you have the right to control your own destiny.  - Linus Torvalds
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this time we will talk about the Week 2 of the coding period for GSoC 2019 and the story of the elusive pull requests which people had to wait almost the whole week for.
The Weekend after the Meeting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 0: Communtiy Bonding Period - A new Beginning</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-0-communtiy-bonding-period-a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-0-communtiy-bonding-period-a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Empowerment of individuals is a key part of what makes open source work, since in the end, innovations tend to come from small groups, not from large, structured efforts.  - Tim O&amp;rsquo;Reilly
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and today I would like to tell you about the Community Bonding Period of GSoC 2019 and also talk about my project and organization in detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1: Let the Grind Begin</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/05/week-1-let-the-grind-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/05/week-1-let-the-grind-begin/</guid>
      <description>The joy of coding Python should be in seeing short, concise, readable classes that express a lot of action in a small amount of clear code, not in reams of trivial code that bores the reader to death  - Guido van Rossum
 Welcome everyone, I am your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and I will be barraging you with blogs of my progress with my GSoC project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Journey</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/04/welcome-to-my-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/04/welcome-to-my-journey/</guid>
      <description>Hello Everyone, I am Sc0rpi0n101(Nikhil Maan). I am a Junior at Amity University, Noida with a Computer Science Major. I am a student developer and I have worked with C/C++ for a few years and Python for a few months. I am also learning Fortran currently for my GSoC project and plan to learn full stack Python development in the hope of creating my websites and this blog in full stack instead of Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>