<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source on Sc0rpi0n&#39;s Journey</title>
    <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source on Sc0rpi0n&#39;s Journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4: The Fortran Parser is finally here</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-4-the-fortran-parser-is-finally-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-4-the-fortran-parser-is-finally-here/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When someone says: &amp;lsquo;I want a programming language in which I need only say what I wish done&amp;rsquo;, give him a lollipop.&amp;rdquo;  — Alan J. Perlis in Software Metrics
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week has been relatively a little odd. The week started a little slow but slowly it turned out to be a good and productive week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5: The Evaluation is here: End of Phase 1</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-5-the-evaluation-is-here-end-of-phase-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-5-the-evaluation-is-here-end-of-phase-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On two occasions I have been asked [by members of Parliament!]: &amp;lsquo;Pray, Mr. Babbage, if you put into the machine wrong figures, will the right answers come out ?&amp;rsquo; I am not able rightly to apprehend the kind of confusion of ideas that could provoke such a question.&amp;rdquo; — Charles Babbage
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this week was the last week of Phase-1 and the evaluations for the first phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3: What&#39;s Happening? Where have I been?</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-3-whats-happening-where-have-i-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-3-whats-happening-where-have-i-been/</guid>
      <description>“How did it get so late so soon?”  ― Dr. Seuss
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and we&amp;rsquo;re running late on everything this week. This time we will talk about some operating system stuff along with the week&amp;rsquo;s work. I will have more blogs on operating systems and that type of stuff soon. For now, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what&amp;rsquo;s happening.
Why so Late?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: A Tale of The Illusive Pull Request</title>
      <link>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-2-a-tale-of-the-illusive-pull-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sc0rpi0n101.github.io/2019/06/week-2-a-tale-of-the-illusive-pull-request/</guid>
      <description>In real open source, you have the right to control your own destiny.  - Linus Torvalds
 Welcome everyone, this is your host Nikhil Maan aka Sc0rpi0n101 and this time we will talk about the Week 2 of the coding period for GSoC 2019 and the story of the elusive pull requests which people had to wait almost the whole week for.
The Weekend after the Meeting</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>